Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: English Manuscripts
  - Rameau, Patrick. 'Rosaries', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 310)
  - Rault, Antoine. 'Alone at Last', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 311)
  - Reinert, Jean. 'Le Don J.', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 312)
  - Renard, Jules. 'Pas de Deux. adapted by Adrian Brown', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 313)
  - RenYves. 'Corv, undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 314)
  - Rensenhouse, John. (adaptor). The Anatomy of a Nap', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 315)
  - Reza, Yasmina. Post Mortem', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 316)
  - Reza, Yasmina. 'Until Night. adapted by Caroline and Dana Westberg', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 317)
  - Rezvani, Serge. The Winter Place', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 318)
  - Ribes, Jean-Michel. 'A Walk in the Wood', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 319)
  - Rivi, Alain. 'The Actor', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 320)
  - Rocheman, Lionel. 'Grand-Pa Schlomo', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 321)
  - Romanovsky, Dmitry. 'Crime and Painting', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 322)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Cat as Cat Can', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 323)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Multiple Choice', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 324)
  - Rossett, Alan. 'Les Au Pair', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 325)
  - Roussel, Raymond. 'Heliocentric. adapted by Quincy Long and Kathleen Dimmick', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 326)
  - Roy, Louise and Saia, Louis. Single', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 327)
  - Rullier, Christian. 'Annabelle and Zina', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 328)
  - Rullier, Christian. 'Mass Murder in Paris 320 Dead 800 Wounded', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 329)
  - Salacrou, Armand. 'Boulevard Durand', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 330)
  - Salacrou, Armand. 'The World Is Round', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 331)
  - Santos, Emma. 'The Theatre of Emma Santos', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 332)
  - Sarraute, Nathalie. 'Just for Nothing', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 333)
  - Sartre, Jean-Paul. 'No Exit', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 334)
  - Satie, Erik. 'The String of the Jellyfish', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 335)
  - SchehadGeorges. 'Vasco', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 336)
  - SchehadGeorges. 'Violets', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 337)
  - Schevill, James. 'Shadows of Memory', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 338)
  - Segal, Gilles. 'The Puppetmaster of Lodz', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 339)
  - Segal, Gilles. 'The Puppetmaster of Lodz (first draft)', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 399a.)
  - Semprun-Maura, Carlos. 'Brandy Blues', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 340)
  - Shea, John E. 'La Table', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 341)
  - Sigrid, Jean. 'The Hitch-hiker', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 342)
  - Simon, Jean Yves. 'Good Night, Mister Williams', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 343)
  - Sinelnikoff, Michael. 'Just Like the Movies. adapted by Claire De', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 344)
  - Sirois, Serge. Apple Trees in Bloom', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 345)
  - Tansi, Sony Labou. 'I, the Undersigned Cardiac', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 346)
  - Thme, Victoria. 'A Staircase to Cheer', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 347)
  - Thme, Victoria. 'Stairway to Happiness', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 348)
  - Tiber, Elliot and Ernotte, Andre. 'Broadway Brou-Ha-Ha', undated; 31142040610514 (Box II.9, Folder 349)
  - Tilly. 'Little Black Sambo or Golliwag', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 350)
  - Tilly. 'Les Trompettes de la Mort. adapted by Jack Garfein and Tilly', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 351)
  - Tilly, Frans-Louis. Deli', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 352)
  - Tremblay, Larry. 'The Dragonfly of Chicoutimi', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 353)
  - Tremblay, Larry. 'The Dragonfly of Chicoutimi', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 354)
  - 'The Ubu Guide to New French Language Plays in English Translation, A Selection', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 355)
  - Vaillancourt, Lise. 'Marie-Antoinette, Opus One', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 356)
  - Valentin, Dominique. Miss Martha Jane Canary in the Melodramatic Role of Calamity Jane', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 357)
  - Van Cauwelaert, Didier. 'Heavenly Body. adapted by Roger MacDougall', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 358)
  - Van Itallie, Jean-Claude. Ancient Boys', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 359)
  - Van Itallie, Jean-Claude. 'Paradise Ghetto', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 360)
  - Van Westrenen, Pieter Anton. 'Mondrian..?', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 361)
  - Van Westrenen, Pieter Anton. 'The Breaking', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 362)
  - Various Authors. 'Six Plays/Playwrights from Quebec', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 363)
  - Vaulthier, Jean. The Character Against Himself' or (Fortissimo), undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 364)
  - Vian, Boris. 'The Empire Builders', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 365)
  - Vinaver, Michel. Chamber Theater (Dissident Goes Without Saying and Nina, It'sDifferent), undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 366)
  - Vinaver, Michel. Chamber Theater (Dropout and Nina, That's Something Else), undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 367)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'Customer Service May I Help You?', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 368)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'The Everyday', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 369)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'Hotel Iphigenia', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 370)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'The Interview', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 371)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'The Neighbors', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 372)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'The Ordinary', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 373)
  - Vinaver, Michel. 'A Smile on the End of the Line', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 374)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Always Together', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 375)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'Class Photo', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 376)
  - Visdei, Anca. 'My Callas', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 377)
  - Vitrac, Roger. 'Victor or The Children Take Charge', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 378)
  - Vitrac, Roger. 'Victor or Children Take Over', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 379)
  - Vitrac, Roger. 'Victor ou Les Enfants au Pouvoir', undated; 31142040610522 (Box II.10, Folder 380)
  - Voletti, Michael. 'One of Those', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 381)
  - Volkoff, Vladimir. 'The Interrogation', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 382)
  - Vrebos, Pascal. 'Polycarpe Reincarnate. adapted by Robert M. Hammond', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 383)
  - Vrebos, Pascal. 'Sade-Sock or How to Live After the Asprocalisp. adapted by Robert M. Hammond', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 384)
  - Vrebos, Pascal. 'Yalta 2000', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 385)
  - Vu, Khac Khoan. 'Genghis Khan', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 386)
  - Webb, Mary H. 'Artaud and His Double', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 387)
  - Weill, Alain Didier. 'Vienna 13', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 388)
  - Weingarten, Romain. 'Snow', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 389)
  - Westphal, Eric. 'Playing Mozart. adapted by Mark Valencia and Tom Pomfret', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 390)
  - Westphal, Eric. The Scent of Honey', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 391)
  - Westphal, Eric. 'You and Your Clouds', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 392)
  - White, Edgar Nkosi. 'The Garden', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 393)
  - White, Edgar Nkosi. 'When Night Turn Day (Three Kings Darkly)', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 394)
  - Willems, Paul. 'It's Raining in My House', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 395)
  - Wittig, Monique. 'The Constant Journey', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 396)
  - Wittig, Monique. 'La Recrion', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 397)
  - Worms, Jeanine. 'Archiflore', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 398)
  - Worms, Jeanine. 'La Boutique', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 399)
  - Worms, Jeanine. 'Duetto', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 400)
  - Worms, Jeanine. 'Pardon Monsieur', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 401)
  - Worms, Jeanine. 'With or Without Trees', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 402)
  - Zeig, Sande. (adaptor). 'Behind the Heart', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 403)
  - Zinsou, Senouvo Agbota. 'The Singing Tortoise', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 404)
  - Zinsou, Senouvo Agbota. 'Yevi's Adventures in Monsterland', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 405)
  - Zola, Emile. 'Thse Raquin', undated; 31142040610530 (Box II.11, Folder 406)